oneweek.co.uk 2016-12-30

# Security & Privacy | Health To Happiness

At Health to Happiness Ltd. we are committed to protecting your privacy and your Personal Information will be handled by us with the greatest care at all time. This Privacy Policy sets out how we use your Personal Information and the measures we have implemented to protect it.

We may collect and process the following data about you:

• Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site or any of our other site. This includes information provided at the time of subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our site. 

• If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 

• We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them. 

• Details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfilment of your orders. 

• Details of your visits to our site [including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

 **Your Personal Information**

The Personal Information you provide to us when you return an order voucher by mail or order by phone, email or online will be stored and used to process your order, deliver the products you have requested and maintain up-to-date transactional and shipment records, billing and payment records and customer contact records. From time to time we may use your contact details (name and address, telephone and/or mobile number and/or email address) if we need to contact you for any reason concerning your order or your account. By supplying your Personal Information to us, you agree that we may process it for the purposes set out here.

We may also use your contact details to keep you up to date by mail phone or email (where you have supplied an email address for this purpose) with information on products and services or to provide details of our special offers. If you decide at any time that you do not wish to receive any further marketing information from us, simply contact us to notify us of this and we will remove your contact details from all our internal mailing lists.

 **Information Disclosure**

It will be necessary for us to disclose certain details of your Personal Information to our employees and agents to enable us, amongst other things, to deliver the items you have ordered deal with customer queries and requests and process and collect your payments. All external processing for these purposes will be carried out on our direct instructions as Data Controller and under conditions of strict security. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

We may, as necessary, disclose your Personal Information to ensure our compliance with any applicable legal requirements or if required to by court order or in the context of legal proceedings or if it is relevant in the context of a merger or acquisition.

 **Security and Confidentiality**

Health to Happiness Ltd. and its agents use appropriate security measures to provide reasonable precautions against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the Personal Information we collect. Our employees and agents who have access to your Personal Information are bound by strict confidentiality obligations.

 **IP Addresses & Cookies**

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is a small text file placed on your hard disk by your Web Browser when you visit a Web site and are used to store information about you and your preferences for the site. Only the information you provide or the choices you make while visiting a Web site can be stored in a cookie. We use cookies on this site in order to make it easier and quicker for you to navigate the site on future visits. However if you do not wish to use this facility, the Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.
